A dedicated and highly motivated Software Engineer with a strong technical foundation, a passion for learning, and a collaborative mindset. Proven experience in executing full lifecycle software development (SDLC), while producing well-designed and functional code.

Work History

2023-06 -

Certified Nursing Assistant

Current Preston Greens, Lexington, KY

- Provide personal assistance and routine daily care to over 100 residents
- Enhance the residents' independence and quality of life
- Provide treatment, care, and support for people with dementia.

2023-02 -2023-06

International Account Representative

Total Quality Logistics, Lexington, KY

- Communicate with sales team and customers to build and maintain ongoing relationships
- Manage daily shipment activities, resolving issues to ensure pickup and delivery is on time
- Assist with billing and accounting responsibilities as needed.

2022-05 -2023-02

Production Team Member

Toyota Motor Manufacturing Kentucky, Georgetown, KY

- Used established assembly instructions to complete jobs quickly, accurately and with zero errors
- Conducted quality assurance inspections on finished components and identified issues
- Identified machinery malfunctions by performing troubleshooting tasks.

Education

2021-01 -2023-09

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science W/conc in Software Engineering

Southern New Hampshire University

- summa cum laude graduate
- Honor Roll and President's List: https://meritpages.com/JSloan00
- Relevant Coursework: system analysis and design, software development lifecycle, UI/UX design, software testing and automation, software security, client/server development, mobile architecture and programming, full stack development I & II, and software reverse engineering.

Jaelyn Sloan

Software Engineer

Contact

Address

Georgetown, KY 40324

Phone

(502)395-3018

E-mail

Jaelynsloan@outlook.com

Skills

C/C++

Python

Java

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Angular

React

Node.js

MongoDB